- Oh, dear!
- What?
(Sheldon:)Raj's television.
(Sheldon:)I just realized
(Sheldon:)we're about to spend an evening
watching a plasma screen
(Sheldon:)with a cluster of dead pixels
in the upper left-hand corner.
(Leonard:)So don't watch TV.
(Leonard:)Read a book.
(Sheldon:)And be a social pariah?
(Sheldon:)Oh, you know
that's not my style.
(Leonard:)Ugh!
(Sheldon:)The audible sigh is a show
of exasperation, right?
(Leonard:)Right.
(Sheldon:)Is it about me
or the dead pixels?
(Raj:)Hey, you're
just in time.
(Raj:)We made Tex-Mex.
(Leonard:)Oh, sounds great.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Indians
making Tex-Mex.
(Sheldon:)Might as well have had
the Chinese pizza.
(Raj:)Hey, you.
(Leonard:)Hi.
(Howard:)That's got to be fun
for you, huh?
(Howard:)Watching Hofstadter
suck the saliva
(Howard:)out of your sister's mouth?
(Sheldon:)Excuse me. Before this evening
goes any further,
(Sheldon:)we need to decide
where everyone is going to sit.